## Giedrė Stašionė



DATE OF BIRTH 1988-03-16 (34y.)

CELLPHONE NO. 61847077

ADDRESS Žirgelių g. Kaunas

E-MAIL giedre.stasione@gmail.com

INTERESTS IT, telecommunication

## Introduction

In the past 1.5 year I was learning frontend development as I have decided to change my career completely. So far I have learned and have experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Redux, Node.js, MongoDb, even a little with React Native. Now I am practicing Typescript.

I am looking for a team which could help me grow as a professional. I am learning fast and eager to get real experience in the tech company. I am ready to dive deep in the work, to be a team member, to grow as a professional and as a person. I believe I can be a valuable member of a company and a team.

I am a mentee at Women Go Tech, Frontend track.

My GitHub: https://github.com/Gie-sta

You are welcome to connect with me via LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/giedre-stasione.

**EXPECTED JOB LEVEL** 

Junior Specialist

## Work experience

2015-11 - 2021-03

## **Chief Specialist**

Financial Crime Investigation Service

#### **WORK DESCRIPTION**

- My responsibility was to research economic and financial activities according to the accounting documents of companies and present a conclusion. Maternity leave since 2017-05
- What I bring: Proven ability to learn fast as I started working with no experience in accounting. Strong ownership, because sometimes needed to defend my conclusions of research as expert in the court.

#### **DEPARTMENTS**

- Finance, accounting, audit
- Public sector

#### 2010-10 - 2015-11

## Tax advisors team leader, tax advisor

State Tax Inspectorate

#### WORK DESCRIPTION

- As a tax advisor I was consulting taxpayers in a call center by answering inbound calls or written inquiries. As team lead, I was responsible for the quality of the team inbound calls, training of new employees, assessment of the quality of the consultations, collection of new and relevant legal information, analysis of legal acts, and provision of comments.
- What I bring: Proven ability to learn fast, communicate with customers and team, share my knowledge with team as I have started as junior tax advisor, after a few years I was put in charge of a group of 10 people. Ability to master new technologies because I needed to learn new features like EDS, Mano VMI and advise taxpayers and team members how to use them and many others internal systems to evaluate sensitive information about paid taxes and debts.

#### **DEPARTMENTS**

Public sector

## Education

2010 – 2012

## **Mykolas Romeris University**

Finance

2006 - 2010

## **Kaunas University of Technology**

Public administration

# Language skills

• Lithuanian	native	
<ul><li>English</li></ul>	speak well	write well
<ul><li>Russian</li></ul>	speak little	write little

# Computer skills

<ul><li>Bootstrap</li></ul>	1 to 3 years
• CSS	1 to 3 years
• Express.js	1 to 3 years
• Git	Up to 1 year
• HTML5	1 to 3 years
<ul><li>JavaScript</li></ul>	1 to 3 years
<ul><li>MongoDB</li></ul>	1 to 3 years
<ul><li>Node.js</li></ul>	1 to 3 years
<ul><li>React,js</li></ul>	Up to 1 year
<ul><li>SASS</li></ul>	1 to 3 years
<ul><li>Typescript</li></ul>	Up to 1 year

## Courses and seminars

2021 y. Modern React with Redux

52,5 hours

Organizer: Udemy

I have certification

The Web Developer Bootcamp 2021

63 hours

Organizer: Udemy

I have certification

Modern HTML & CSS From The Beginning 2020 y.

21 hours

Organizer: Udemy

I have certification

"Atrask Technologijas"

Women Go Tech 3 mėnesių nuotolinė programa "Atrask Technologijas"

Organizer: Women Go Tech

I have certification

# Membership

2022 - Now

**Women Go Tech** 

mentee

**ACHIEVEMENTS** 

## Other information

DRIVING LICENCE FROM

2008-09 (B category)

PERSONAL SKILLS:

I look at the tasks entrusted to me responsibly and perform them with quality. I am a fast and good learner and able to teach others, I am always ready to help both customers and colleagues.

PAGE: **4/4**